= kisskh.asia =
♪ From primal chaos to the starry sky ♪
♪ In the whole world, we shall hold the balance ♪
♪ The cauldron tempers divine blades ♪
♪ The furnace refines the empty void ♪
♪ The Way is in mystic fate ♪
♪ Be brave enough to split the primal chaos wide open ♪
[Pull Strings]
[Adapted from the novel by Yan Gui Zheng Zhuan]
Changgeng.
How could I ever forget that name?
All my failures
are all thanks to him.
I want revenge.
I'm going to kill him.
The South Sea battle was very costly.
You haven't recovered yet.
Just rest and recuperate for now.
As for other things,
pay them no mind.
Right.
Pay no mind.
Master Jin Chan,
about the Sea Deity Sect...
Ao Yi returning to the Dragon Palace now
is no coincidence.
It's Changgeng's scheme.
He's here to avenge the Ascendance Sect.
Pity our Crown Prince
has been so restless lately,
unfit for big tasks.
His downfall came from two events:
Jiang Si'er leaving him,
and his defeat in the South Sea.
Both were caused
by Changgeng.
Master, you mean...
He saw through our scheme,
so he wants to ruin First Prince,
support Ao Yi,
and crush our plot.
That despicable Changgeng.
Now the Crown Prince is useless.
West dawn's grand plot
probably can't rely on him.
How about we...
The First Prince
is a pawn we planted long ago.
Can't abandon him easily.
Changgeng can ruin my pawn,
so why can't I ruin his?
[Episode 23]
Senior.
Here.
I gathered all kinds of herbs
and made this sachet for you.
Sniff it now and then.
Thanks, Senior.
How is it?
Seems like.
I really can smell it.
Liar.
Just remember,
you belong to Turtle Island now.
If anyone outside picks on you,
don't worry.
I will teach them a lesson for you.
Once I revive the Dragon Clan and rule the East Sea,
I will find you.
Whatever the Dragon Clan owes you,
I'll repay my debt to you
a hundred times over.
Who's there?
Please rise.
Why are you still here?
We came to bring you fresh clothes.
We thought we'd help you change.
You don't need to do that anymore.
I can wash and dress by myself.
Well...
You may go back.
Yes.
Please show me the way.
Senior is such a big perv.
He sees a beautiful fairy and he...
Oops.
Lan Ling'e.
Don't talk about Senior like that.
Since he has gone astray,
I must be his guiding light.
I'm coming.
Senior.
Senior, where are you?
Is it because my legs are too short?
Senior. Senior.
No, my legs are pretty long.
Senior, you left no footprints.
Senior.
What to do?
Not bad.
Jiu...
Ling'e.
Seems Changshou
quietly set up a formation here.
Aunt, why are you here?
As expected of Senior Changshou.
Even predicted us tailing him.
Changshou is such a big perv.
When he sees a lovely fairy...
- Exactly.
- No.
He was bewitched and led astray.
Grandlord entrusted me with a heavy duty.
I must protect everyone.
This time,
let me be a guiding light
to protect Senior Changshou.
You two were eavesdropping on me.
What did you say?
We all came for Senior,
so our hearts must be aligned.
Too bad Changshou outsmarted us.
Looks like we can't stop him today.
Protecting Senior is our duty.
Well said.
Starting today,
our Changshou's Guardian Trio
is officially formed.
Exactly, we're gonna split them...
No. Protect Senior.
Who's over there?
Hide.
Yunxiao.
Why are you here?
Let me tell you,
never act recklessly.
If you ruin the grand plan,
the consequences will be...
Good evening, Yunxiao.
Well, I...
The Dragon Palace is huge.
Hard to find the restroom.
Stop right there.
Who are you?
Do I know you?
A low-tier human disciple like you,
visiting me late at night, what do you want?
Wanting to steal a few spell lessons,
or fishing for romance?
No, I...
Even a brat like you from the Human Clan
can be a cultivator?
You dare say our Seizing Sect recruits recklessly?
If it weren't for the Dragon Palace,
I'd teach you a lesson for sure.
Get lost.
Yes, yes.
Sorry to disturb you.
Dear friends,
His Majesty has ordered
that you eat and drink well today.
You must enjoy yourselves.
I, Turtle, will raise a toast first.
Take a bite.
Fill it up for me.
What is Yunxiao...
Aunt. Senior.
Junior.
Senior.
I quit drinking. You go ahead.
Okay.
Where are you going?
Off to work.
Work?
What for?
Our Sea Deity Sect loves working.
Work brings joy. All together now.
Bear Island is so great. We love Bear Island.
Listen to the deity. And we'll live forever.
Let's go.
Alright.
Come on.
Make way.
What are you doing?
Working.
Are you crazy?
Right.
Where am I going with them?
The Sea Deity Sect's brainwashing
is way too strong.
We gotta be careful.
High immortal.
High immortal?
High immortal!
Calling me?
High immortal.
Let's have a drink.
Bottoms up.
Let's drink to...
Oh my.
So blunt?
Who did the Celestial Court send?
Could it be the Immortal of Wine?
Your Majesty.
I don't think there's such post.
Right. No such position.
Let me ask.
High immortal.
In the Celestial Court, what's your post?
Changshou, what should I say?
What position exactly?
Tell the truth.
High immortal, what's your position?
Seems hard of hearing.
Your Majesty.
I serve in the Marriage Division,
managing Three Realms marriages,
known to people
as Moon Elder.
Moon Elder?
Moon Elder.
Could you tie a red thread for me?
Just one is enough, please.
Me first.
I was here first.
One at a time.
Everyone gets a match.
Enough!
How do I usually teach you?
Over a bit of personal romance,
you've shamed our Dragon Palace
before the Celestial Immortal.
Get out.
Shrimps can't get married.
Alright?
Shrimps can't, but dragons can.
Moon Elder, I'm truly sorry.
Excuse the embarrassment.
On their behalf, I apologize to you.
No need for that.
Let's share an arm-crossed...
No, a heart-to-heart drink.
Moon Elder,
I wanna get a few more concubines.
What do you say?
Dragon King, you're so...
So vigorous.
This is outrageous.
Our East Sea Dragon Clan
is the head of dragons,
master of the Four Seas.
The envoy the Celestial Court sent
is just a petty marriage clerk.
What?
Looking down on us?
Don't get angry.
Jia, why such a temper?
Since the Celestial Court sent this high immortal here,
that means
it hasn't forgotten our Dragon Clan.
That's a good thing.
Yeah.
Why so angry? Come on.
Father, you are mistaken.
If the Celestial Court truly valued us,
they'd send a mighty general
to spar with our warriors.
If he truly has the skill,
we'd naturally be convinced.
But now,
sending a mere Moon Elder?
May I ask what power you have?
What stage are you cultivated to?
The liquor's gone cold.
Jia makes a point.
It's gone cold.
No, wait.
Since you're a Deity from heaven,
you must know some magical power.
Show us a trick for everyone to see.
I only tie threads.
Well,
I, Ao Jia, Crown Prince of the Dragon Palace,
would be honored to amuse the high immortal.
Please.
Switching from drinking to fighting?
What?
I'm not...
Scared?
I'm scared? I...
Father.
I have something to report.
Tell me later.
Moon Elder came this time
precisely because
the Celestial Court granted me a marriage.
Little Prince is getting married?
Congratulations.
Yi, such a huge matter,
why didn't you tell me earlier?
Which lady is it?
Can she match East Sea's Second Prince?
Father.
She is...
Speak up. Who is it?
Mermaid Princess Jiang Si'er.
By Celestial Emperor's decree,
I am willing to marry Ao Yi.
You?
Get married?
That's right.
But...
Why make me get married?
Because you must lead the East Sea
to manage the Forbidden Land.
Managing forbidden land lets you fight the Westdawn Sect.
Fighting the Westdawn Sect
requires leading the East Sea,
and replacing your brother Ao Jia.
So...
So,
you want me to marry Si'er?
Exactly.
If it can stop the Great Tribulation,
I can accept that.
No way.
I always take Si'er as my sister-in-law.
How can I marry her?
Kings of East Sea Dragon Clan
historically intermarry with Mermaids
to secure our support.
This is strategy.
So,
I can accept it.
Your Highness, you said
if Changgeng asked a favor,
you'd complete the mission he gave you.
Right?
I did say that.
So you came to ask for my advice
because of the mission.
Changgeng gave you,
didn't you?
You do have good ideas, but...
Your returning this time
is for the Great Tribulation,
allowing zero room for error.
For the Three Realms,
and to fulfill Changgeng's mission,
can't you just sacrifice a tiny bit?
Can't you?
I promise it'll be a fake marriage.
Nothing intimate will ever happen.
How's that?
Are you hot?
No, I'm just feeling thrilled.
Because we discussed some
rather embarrassing topics.
Li Changshou.
If I agree to this,
can you help me find my Senior?
Of course.
Once you become King of East Sea,
and with the Celestial Court's help,
finding someone will be effortless.
What did you say?
Jia.
Quiet. I haven't asked her yet.
Father.
Jiang Si'er broke an engagement once.
And it was you who decreed
that Dragon and Mermaid Clans cut ties.
The East Sea is the head of the Four Seas.
How can she just leave at will
and return whenever she pleases?
Dragon King.
Here's the deal.
In the Celestial Court,
I oversee all marriages in the Three Realms.
I've come this time
to make this marriage happen.
To show the Celestial Court's sincerity,
we've prepared a generous gift.
Here you go.
Void Retrieval?
Impressive.
Senior.
You used your spell.
In the Primordial Era's Witch-Demon War,
the Ancestral Witch heirs used the blood
of their ancestors to forge a sword.
It was called
the Pregenesis Sword.
In the Deity-Demon War 1,000 years ago,
the Demon Emperor got his hands on it.
Relying on this Pregenesis Sword,
he drenched the Three Realms in blood.
It counters magic, but not Demonic Arts.
That's how the Demon Emperor
tore through the Three Realms.
You really know it well.
But sadly, the sword was split in three.
What I hold in my hand
is one of those three pieces.
Yes, exactly.
This is Pregenesis Sword.
I recognize it.
If you agree
to let Ao Yi and Jiang Si'er
marry within three days,
Celestial Court is willing to give you
the fragment
as a gesture of our sincerity.
Are these words true?
Absolutely true.
Good.
Yi.
Do you two really wish to marry?
Father.
I do.
I do too.
Done.
Turtle Minister, come on, drink.
Come. Sit here.
Come on.
Come.
Perfect. Come on.
Come on.
Jiang Si'er.
You're driving a wedge between us brothers.
What do you take East Sea for?
What do you take me for?
I just recognized
who's weak inside,
and who's a true hero.
How dare you?
Please.
You want
to fight me?
Brother,
Si'er
is my betrothed.
I can't let you hurt her.
Si'er?
Betrothed?
Fine. If you mean to wed,
defeat me first.
To lead the Dragon Clan,
you must defeat your brother.
Brother.
For the Dragon Clan.
I must win.
Enough talk.
Just fight.
Surrender.
Growing up,
when have you ever beaten me?
Senior, you're still not acting?
No need.
But Little Prince is gonna lose.
Let's keep watching.
I'm sorry.
I can't lose.
Dragon Flow.
How did you spot my true form?
Your power is indeed strong,
but compared to opponents I met in the Mortal Realm,
you still fall short.
Senior.
I will protect you.
Ao Yi absorbed Cloudlink Hermit's Resonance,
gaining at least 1,000 years of spiritual power.
Plus his Dragon's Prophecy,
he now has Aureate Immortal strength.
Ao Jia is no match.
No.
This won't do.
Let's try again.
Ao Jia.
We are blood brothers.
To restore the Dragon Clan,
I need your help.
Brother.
Join me in restoring the Dragon Clan.
Alright?
Blood bonds and affection are all illusions.
What's wrong?
All is nothingness. All arts void.
Shielding Formation. Open.
Blood Gnat.
Paper butterflies.
Transformation.
Formation.
These moves,
I've seen them all.
Think I wouldn't be prepared?
Changgeng.
Brother.
What's wrong?
Jiang Si'er.
Now I'll show you
who rules the East Sea.
Transform into a dragon.
You can't transform here.
Drink up.
Drink.
Transform into a dragon.
Why doesn't he transform into a dragon?
It's not that he doesn't want to.
He just can't.
He can't?
Have you ever wondered
why he grew so slowly
after years in the Dragon Palace?
Someone restrains him?
Junior.
I have a task for you.
What?
Later, stir up trouble back there.
The bigger the better.
How do I do that?
Do whatever you want.
Go now.
Alright.
Me.
Who?
Who is it?
Let's celebrate.
My goodness.
Impressive.
Voidcity agreed to go to Blood Sea and save your clan.
Cultivator.
What's wrong?
Cultivator Wen Jing.
What is it?
I was defeated by Changgeng.
Transform into a dragon, now.
I can't do it.
You are ready now.
Your Highness.
Ao Jia using his dragon form against you
already disregards brotherly affection.
Since he treats you like this,
why bother showing him mercy?
Nice assist.
Transform into a dragon!
Ancestral Dragon?
Ao Yi?
It was you?
Brother.
I won.
Ao Jia,
using your dragon form to sneak-attack your brother,
so ruthless and heartless,
how do you deserve to rule the East Sea?
I didn't.
Just now I...
I
I lost.
A deal's a deal.
A deal's a deal, right?
I wish you two
love and happiness.
Brother.
In that case,
no one objects
to the marriage
between Ao Yi and Jiang Si'er, right?
Good.
Three days later,
we'll hold the wedding ceremony.
Turtle Minister, hurry and prepare.
Yes.
Congratulations, Dragon King.
Attendant.
The jug is empty.
Bring another jug.
I showed him mercy today,
but he fought me to the death.
If he weren't my brother,
I wouldn't have lost.
Indeed, the First Prince held back.
Little Prince is being unreasonable.
Right.
Golden dragon.
The golden dragon we encountered
in the South Sea that day
was actually Ao Yi.
You were sneak-attacked then,
unrecovered from severe wounds,
that's why Little Prince
had a chance today.
Have you ever considered
that the South Sea matter
was also a scheme?
Ao Yi is my brother.
What scheme could there be?
If that golden dragon was his true form,
why didn't he reveal himself to you
when you were in the South Sea?
Well, maybe it's because...
Right.
Ever since Changgeng appeared,
the Little Prince has stopped obeying you.
He left the East Sea without permission to train,
transformed into a dragon and attacked you, leaving you wounded.
And now, while you're still recovering,
he defeated you in front of everyone.
Right.
A scheme.
He had long coveted your place.
So he joined forces with Changgeng
to take what you love
and wound your spirit.
He is no longer your brother.
He is
your enemy.
Right.
Ao Yi
is my enemy.
is my...
You'll always be my brother.
Join me in restoring the Dragon Clan.
Alright?
No.
Ao Yi is not my enemy.
Ao Yi is my brother.
First Prince, you've worked hard today.
Get some rest.
Master Jin Chan.
You...
This pawn is useless now.
Take him to the East Palace.
Lock him in his room and keep him there.
Master, you mean,
confine the First Prince?
Killing him is too much trouble.
Well played, Changgeng.
He ruined a pawn of mine.
Your victory today
is absolutely crucial. Congratulations.
Did I hurt my brother?
You brothers
will have plenty of time to mend the bonds later.
Right now, we must
make good use of this victory.
But I never meant to hurt him.
Our actions this time
concern the safety of the Dragon Clan
and even the safety of the Three Realms.
Is there truly no other way?
Must I beat my brother?
In today's battle,
if you hadn't given it your all,
you would've been hurt by him.
On the battlefield, that's the rule.
You either strike first, or you get struck down.
Your Highness.
The strength and wisdom you've shown today
are nothing like the person I first met.
You've changed completely.
If Changgeng could see
how much you've changed,
he'd surely be happy for you.
Right.
I owe it all to the armor you gave me.
What?
I mean...
This armor. You gave it to me.
I did?
That day, the maids brought me some clothes.
Hidden within them was an armor sealed by power.
Their cultivation was too weak to see through it.
They thought it was ordinary clothes
and gave it to me.
Did I?
I must say, you human disciple
are remarkably considerate.
Thanks to your suit of armor,
he would've been hurt today otherwise.
This armor is a rare treasure indeed.
Invulnerable to weapons.
And you kept this from us?
Playing it so safe.
When that dragon
had you pinned down,
he was the one
who told me to call out to you
and tell you to transform and fight back.
Did I say that?
♪ See mortal joys and sorrows ♪
♪ Reunions and partings, as fate unfolds ♪
♪ Alas, love has many twists and turns ♪
♪ Memories filled with sorrow ♪
♪ Slowly, wishes turn to regret ♪
♪ You've gone afar, like mist fading ♪
♪ Tearfully, this life's bond is not over ♪
♪ Past fragments vanish into night ♪
♪ Down a few more cups of wine ♪
♪ Through land and sea, I ask you to come ♪
♪ For honor's sake, upright and grand ♪
♪ Alas, our story is short ♪
♪ Slowly, wishes turn to regret ♪
♪ You've gone afar, like mist fading ♪
♪ Tearfully, this life's bond is not over ♪
♪ Past fragments vanish into night ♪